[{"answer": "Well, it is a physical pain as well.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Is it just an emotional pain or is it also a medically diagnosable physical pain?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Hi.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "When was the last time you said, \"hello\" to a stranger passing you on the street, to a friend you hadn't seen in years?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Does she do that?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Have you have periods of genuine loneliness?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "I actually did because there is a difference between being alone and being lonely, don't you think?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Yeah, I've had periods where I've been lonely, you know, and I think that, you know, you go through periods of life where you're very busy and so you don't recognize it as much.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Sanjay, have you?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Yeah, you see, I think that's a really interesting point because there must be degrees of this.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Can you be lonely?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "There's loneliness from mourning a loved one, right?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Yeah, you can work from -- you can do that and you realize that you haven't spoken.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "To work from home, is it?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "I'm about to do just that, Gayle.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "When was the last time you said \"hello\" to somebody you didn't know?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Hello.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "You were.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "I know, wasn't that nice of me?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Have you had periods of real genuine loneliness in your life do you think?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Piers, she could live in a house and never turn on a TV.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "I mean how long could you go without any other contact?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "I can't imagine but it's true.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "The key point is to let people know that there is power and you're being able to just say, \"Hello\", thank you Rita Wilson for that.\"", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "What is -- from your point of view, the key points of this campaign?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "She did?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Oh, I think it's both and I think it's certainly is a tool that if you choose to use it as force for good, you can.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "From your experience at social media, is it a force for good or is it also in some way a cover for people perhaps not to interact in the way you just suggested?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "... I was in town and Gayle, didn't I e-mail you like three to four times?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Well, it's not that good.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "How is your British accent coming along Oprah?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Did he say that to you?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Well, I think that it depends upon what you're talking about.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Or is a personal interaction of hearing a voice, seeing somebody, shaking your hand, saying hello, like you said, actually in the end more important?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Oh, screaming is not a part of my life.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Do you have a lot -- have real screaming argument?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "No, I don't scream at anybody.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "In my entire life.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Only two people?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Well, I screamed at more than two people.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Are you a screamer?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Yes, it's amazing.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Does that surprise you Oprah?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Well, you know...", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Sanjay, what is the -- if you know somebody that you think is lonely, what is the best way to try and make them less lonely?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "You know, don't minimize just saying hello.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Other than just saying hello, what else could be done?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "... absolute stuff...", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "ING: Oprah, where are you going?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I'm going home.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Where are you going?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "And I, you know, I just want to echo what you've said that it starts with hello and being able to extend your self, I think for everybody who's watching around the world -- Piers, isn't this amazing, you're around the world every night?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Hi.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Certainly, sir.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Do you have a table for dinner?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "I'm alone.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "How many in your party?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Don't you think Sanjay?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Not necessarily.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Is a loner the same as somebody who is lonely?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "And you can't help thinking Sanjay that if people are able to pick on people and -- who are behaving in that way who appeared to be loners and try and interact with them, I'm sure they do, but if tried harder, you could perhaps avoid some of this trying to this happening because it's the disconnection.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "What was it about that feeling of loneliness, that desperation?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Well, you know, what I think, I think in this age of Instagram and Twitter, we're always posting all the great stuff we're doing.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Gayle, what do think of this?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Well, it's really -- it comes about by just everyday hustle and bustle and even though I have a great family and great girl friends, I think over time we just kind of disconnect ourselves.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Why you're lonely?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "I think that's a better question for you.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Gayle is it a problem that affects more women than men, do you think?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "But I would think so.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Sanjay, what do you think?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Are you worried?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "Yes that interesting.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "What if you're not text savvy at all and you've been excluded from the wider group at school or college or wherever it maybe?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Yes and it's very different than picking up the phone just to be able to see your son's face.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "So it's in the (inaudible)?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "I said, \"What did one elevator say to the other elevator?\"", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "What was the joke?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "Well, it's terrible.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "See, isn't that coming?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "Yeah, you know, it can.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 765, "question": "I would have a follow up to you which is right now, you know, if you're in one of the storm there, just like New York and you have these snow storms, if you're at home on your own, you can't get out for days on end, that, and yourself must make you feel very lonely?", "qSentId": 764}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 789, "question": "What about for other people?", "qSentId": 788}, {"answer": "Yeah, really.", "docId": "140219pmt", "aSentId": 807, "question": "It's been the first time I really said \"Won't buy\" (ph), isn't it?", "qSentId": 806}]